- 进来吧 - 嘿哟
- Come on in. - Hey-o!
- 嗨 - 哈喽
- Hi! - Hello.
喜欢我们的毛衣吗
Do you love our sweaters?
我觉得雪球舞会穿这个一定超赞
I thought they would be perfect for the Snow Ball dance.
就是在卖圣诞饰品
I got them at the store where you buy things
的那种店里买的
that go with the other things.
噢我知道那里 我们就是在那家店买的那个
Oh, I know that place. That's where we got
画着椒盐乐队的胡椒和盐调料罐
our Salt-N-Pepa salt and pepper shakers.
克莱尔永远分不清乐队里谁是谁
Claire can never tell which one is which.
这是个不太好解决的困惑
A confusing idea poorly executed.
别再拐着弯说我种族歧视了
Stop implying I'm a racist.
我们是怎么被骗去当陪护人这种事的
How did we get roped into this chaperone thing?
都是这个无敌烦人的家庭教师协会成员 玛乔丽
This incredibly annoying PTA mom, Marjorie,
一直吵着要我们做一些志愿活动
keeps hounding us to volunteer for things,
我们能用的借口都用完了
and we finally ran out of excuses.
噢 我应该告诉她我们在路上了
Ooh, I should probably tell her we're coming.
难以置信
Unreal.
你到哪了
"Where are you?"
你和克莱尔在一起吗
"Are you with Claire?"
你们还有多远到
"How far away are you?"
快到的时候给我发短信
"Text me when you're close."
我把车钥匙锁车里了
"I locked my keys in my car."
噢 这是海莉发的
Oh, that's from Haley.
虽然我很愿意帮忙促成这个活动
Much as I'd love to meet this dingbat,
他们到底需要几个监护人啊
how many chaperones do they really need?
要淋湿那些死胖子的话 一个人就够了吧
Takes one person to turn a garden hose on those dry humpers.
如果菲尔去的话 你也得去
If Phil is going, you are going.
我才不想变成在场唯一一个没带老公的人
I don't like being the only person in the room without a husband.
没安全感
It's my one insecurity.
菲尔只是想表示友好
Phil's just trying to be nice.
他其实也不想去这种活动
He doesn't want to go to this thing, either.
其实 我还挺期待的
Actually, I was looking forward to it.
也许还可以见到那些所谓的啦啦队员
Maybe meet some of these so-called cheerleaders.
要是我们告诉他们 咱们能空手把人在空中翻个转
Watch their faces when I tell them we could kewpie a scorpion
接着立马分成几列站好 看他们什么表情
into a cradle catch and then pop up into a split extension.
那些事很多现在都是违法的
Most of that stuff's illegal now.
我觉得菲尔其实是想说
I think what Phil's trying to say is that
我们俩已经很久没有过一个男人之夜了
he and I haven't had a boy's night in a good while.
我的意思是 我们就一起消遣不也挺好
I mean, wouldn't it be nice to just hang out together,
就你和我
just you and me?
哥们 你觉得怎么样
What do you say, buddy?
纳尼
What?!
和我哥们杰一起玩玩儿也挺不错
Might be nice to have a hang with my boy Jay.
如果你不介意的话
If it's fine with you.
当然 我也只能帮你到这了
Sure, it's the least I could do, because tomorrow
因为明天是你得陪卢克写作业
you are going to help Luke with his homework
而我就去游览酒之城
while I visit wine country.
我也想去
I want to go.
她指的是
That's just what she calls
躺在蹦床上喝夏敦埃酒
lying on the trampoline drinking Chardonnay.
呃
Ah.
噢 是的 我们在路上了
Oh, yes! We're on our way.
- 好了 - 拜拜
- Okay. - Bye-bye.
- 拜拜 - 你俩好好玩儿啊
- Bye. - Have fun, you two.
不用担心 我们会玩的很嗨的
Don't worry about us. We'll have a blast.
我们会很开心的 我们会很开心的
We'll have a good time. We'll have a good time.
耶
Yes!
今晚一定超赞的
This is gonna be so great!
当然了 等她们离开
Sure it will. Maybe give them about
大概5分钟 你就可以走人了
a five-minute lag time before you hit the road.
什么意思 你
What do you mean? You...
你之前说我们要一起做点啥的
you said we were gonna do something together.
我只是想帮我俩摆脱掉那场愚蠢的舞会
I was just trying to get us out of that stupid dance.
噢
Oh.
- 好吧 - 好好享受今晚吧 菲尔
- Okay. - Enjoy your night, Phil.
我要看一本史诗西部小说 讲的是一个恶警长
I've got a date with an epic Western about a crooked sheriff,
我现在正看到
and I'm at the first of
第一场绞刑呢 估计后面还得吊死好多个人
what I predict to be many wrongful hangings.
好吧 既然你啥也不想干
Well, if you're not up for doing anything,
那我就去舞会了
I think I'll just go to the dance.
什么 不行 你不能去
What? No. You can't do that.
那我看起来不就跟混球一样了吗
Makes me look like a jerk.
- 好吧 那我该干啥呢 - 随便你
- Well, then what am I supposed to do? - Whatever you like.
- 我想去舞会 - 你怎么就没听懂呢
- I want to go to the dance. - How are you not getting this?
好 那我就回家去
Fine. I'll just go home.
你是去舞会 对吧
You're going to the dance, aren't you?
- 当然啦 - 好吧 你赢了
- Of course I am. - All right, you win.
- 我们来玩吧 - 棒棒哒
- We'll do something. - Awesome!
- 你想做什么 - 我的天 我不知道
- What do you want to do? - Gosh, I don't know.
我是说 我还想着跳舞呢
I mean, dancing is still so much in the air.
- 啊啊 - 你去哪啊
- Uh-huh - Where are you going?
苏格兰酒城玩玩吧
Scotch country.
12号桶里冰块不够了
We're low on ice in bucket 12.
嘿 嘿 这些蟹饼得撑一晚上
Hey, hey, those crab cakes have to last all night.
少发点儿 出去躲躲
Push the cheese.
演出曲目呢
Setlist?
你要以Get Lucky开场
You're starting with "Get Lucky"?
搞毛啊你他妈
Come on, we're telling a story here.
你知道现在几点了吗
Do you know what time it is?
我还以为你会帮我布置
I thought you were gonna help me set up.
抱歉啦兄弟 我在烦这幅大图的事
Sorry, buddy. I was worrying about the big-picture stuff.
嗯这里有地方放吗
Hmm. Is there enough room for it here,
还是我应该把它放在后门啊
or should I put it in the back entrance?
呵呵 你这张图确实够格放后门
You can certainly put it in a back entrance.
噢 我的天呐 一切都布置得这么漂亮
Oh, my gosh, doesn't everything look so lovely?
毕竟是高中
Well, it's high school.
不管怎么装饰 这里还是
Dress it up all you want, it's still the place I spent
我被残酷的欺凌折磨了四年的地方
four years being tormented by sadistic bullies.
衬衫不错 米歇尔
Nice shirt, Michelle.
噢你知道吗 时代已经变了
Oh, you know what? Times have changed.
高中的时候 你有想过
In high school, did you ever imagine
自己会和足球教练在一起吗
you'd end up with the football coach?
足球教练吗 噢没有
The football coach? No.
游泳教练阿蒂诺倒是每晚都想
The swim coach, Mr. Artino, almost nightly.
噢 塔克教练 米切尔
Oh, Coach Tucker, Mitchell.
感谢你们来做志愿者
Thank you for volunteering.
我可拒绝不了啊
I couldn't say no.
队里的孩子都快求着我来了
The kids on the team practically begged me.
能成为这么重要的人 影响这么多孩子 实在太令人感动了
It's an amazing thing to matter so much and inspire so many.
噢不 我觉得他们想要你来是因为
Oh, no, I think they just wanted you here
那样他们就能恶搞你了
so they can prank you.
- 嗯 - 是啊
- Hmm? - Yeah.
足球队内部已经准备了一些计划
The football team has something all worked out.
我也不清楚到底是什么 因为
I don't know what it is 'cause I checked out
上次他们停发我薪水 我就没来
after they capped my salary.
但是一般都会搞得乱七八糟的
But there's usually a mess,
你可能会想用一件斗篷遮住那华丽丽的场景
so you might want to throw a poncho over all that finery.
噢 噢 我的天 我太讨厌恶作剧了
Oh. Oh, my God, I hate pranks so much.
现在好了 我会整晚疑神疑鬼
Now I'm gonna spend the whole dance paranoid
想象他们会怎么整我
wondering what they're gonna do.
会不会痛 我会不会被弄哭啊
Is it gonna hurt? Am I gonna cry?
你就是小丑啊
You're a clown.
小丑通常不就是恶搞别人吗
Isn't that mostly just pranking people?
不 才不是 小丑是很有爱而且欢乐的
No, it is not. Clowns are loving and joyful.
你知道吗 我曾经被警告过这类的无知行为
You know what? I was warned about this kind of ignorance.
别让我后悔嫁出马戏团
Don't make me regret marrying outside the big top.
怎么了
What?
我们得盯紧点
We got to keep our eyes peeled
这些小孩们想带酒进来
for kids trying to bring alcohol in here.
今晚不喝酒我会撑不过去的
I cannot make it through this thing without a drink.
玛乔丽 12点方向
Marjorie, 12:00.
噢天呐
Oh, God.
快 假装我们在吵架
Quick, pretend we're having a fight.
- 那她就不会过来了 - 嗯哼
- Then she won't come over here. - Mm-hmm.
你抢了我的遗产 你这个傍大款的
You stole my inheritance, you gold digger!
喔 你这话憋很久了吧
Wow, you had that one ready to go.
你们在这啊
There you are.
收到我的短信了吗
Did you get my texts?
看我就没收了什么
Look what I've already confiscated.
噢 龌龊无耻 我帮你没收了
Oh, shameful. I'll take that.
我还需要志愿者去号召父母们
So, I still need volunteers to call parents
来参加无声竞拍
for silent auction items.
我已经分好了6小时的轮班制
I've divided it into six-hour shifts,
所以如果每半小时换一只耳朵听的话
so if you switch ears every half-hour,
其实也还好啦
it's actually not bad.
我能算上你俩吗
Can I count on you two ladies?
我没时间 但她就不一定了
I'm so busy, but I can't speak for Gloria.
我英语很烂啦
My phone English no so good.
好吧 我有点强人所难了
I get it. I'm a bit of a nag-eroo.
嗯嗯
Mm.
就像我妈常开玩笑说
Like my mom always jokes,
你知道谁会不厌其烦让你麻烦吗
you know who you should bore with this?
你老公啊 噢 对了 他抛弃了你
Your husband. Oh, right, he left you.
那女的好焦虑啊
That woman is so uptight.
- 你知道她需要什么吗 - 嗯
- You know what she needs? - Mm.
男人
A man.
那是老一辈的思想了
That is a very old-fashioned attitude,
不过在这件事上 好像确实如此
which in this case, seems pretty accurate.
男人 男人 男人 上哪找啊
A man, a man, a man. Where can we find one.
嗨咯 Siri 查找 古董巡回秀
Hey, Siri, record "Antiques Roadshow."
想不到人啊
I can't think of anyone.
布朗校长啊
Principal Brown.
他也单身 我们可以撮合他们
He's single. We could fix them up.
- 冬日舞会上耶 - 嗯哼
- At the Winter dance. - Mm-hmm.
好浪漫啊
That's so romantic.
对啊 这样她就顾不上
Yes, and maybe she'll get off our backs
跟我们唠叨不停啦
if she spends more time on hers.
虎父无犬子哈
You really are your father's son.
嘿 你还好吧
Hey, you okay?
那家伙刚当着大家的面取笑我的蝶形领结
Guy just made fun of my bow tie in front of everyone.
还问我是不是想打扮成基佬
Asked if I was trying to look gay.
噢 怎么这样
Oh, that is charming.
看来这么多年过去了 高中还是有这样的事哈
So I-I guess high school hasn't changed that much, has it?
听着 我要你把这个重新戴好
Look, I want you to put this back on
骄傲地戴着
and wear this with pride.
在你扔掉之前这就是湿的 对吗
This was soaking wet before you threw it in there, right?
算了 还是丢了吧 没事的
We're gonna let it go. It's fine.
好了
All right.
那个傻逼在哪
Where is this idiot?
你是想打扮成同志吗
Are you trying to look gay?
因为你一没胸肌 二没雀斑
'Cause you don't have the pecs, the pores,
还没穿紧身裤 拳击手大哥
or the pants for it, slugger.
嘿 这有个你这个过时发型可以接受的小建议
Hey, here's a reference that hairstyle's old enough to get.
这不是电臀舞会
It's not twerking.
是 你就是 你就是个 你是个
Yeah, well, you're just... you're just a... you're a...
- 啊 - 你是个 你是个
- Ah? - you're a... you're a...
我要去跻身舞池去啦
So, I'm gonna go squeeze in a dance real quick
弱智兄弟 你就慢慢回味我的话吧
while you stagger to the end of that sentence.
我是莱斯莉 关 柯林斯 海豚日报的
Leslie Kwan Collins, Daily Dolphin.
我认识你 幼儿园起我们就是朋友了
I know who you are. We've been friends since kindergarten.
能说说你对我所知的这个堪称
Care to comment on what my sources are calling
史上最强雪花球派对 的看法吗
"The best Snow Ball ever?"
当然 但是这次派对的成功
Sure, but I'm not the one responsible
不在于我个人
for this party's success.
大家都有出力
They all are.
我是大家的公仆 这一切都是我应该做的
I'm just a humble servant who made it all happen.
能让我和他说两句嘛 谢谢
Can you excuse us, please? Thank you.
你真不要脸
You are unbelievable.
别 我都听你说了几遍了
Stop. I can't keep hearing this.
这次派对的成功是我的功劳
I'm the one who made all this happen.
你有想过仅仅用八千刀来打造这一切有多难吗
Do you have any idea how hard it is doing all this for $8,000?
- 对 当然没有 因为 - 等 等 等下
- Yeah, of course not, because... - Wait, wait, wait.
这次派对的预算是八百刀
The budget for this was $800.
你竟然花了八千刀 那是一整年的预算啊
You spent $8,000? That's the budget for the whole year.
我发信息问你说 这次雪花球派对预算是多少
I texted you, "What's my budget for the Snow Ball."
你回复说八千刀 还配了张毫无关联的
You replied $8,000, followed by a gratuitous gif
一男的被撞了蛋蛋的动图
of a guy getting hit in the nards.
不要顺着栏杆滑滑板一样 对吧
It's like just don't skateboard down a railing, right?
- 布朗校长 - 有事吗
- Principal Brown. - Yep?
如果我们超过了学生会的预算
If we were to go over with the student council budget,
要弄到一点额外的钱有多难呀
how hard would it be to get a little extra money?
噢 没关系啊
Oh, no problem.
把教师休息室里那幅伦勃朗的画卖掉就好啦
We would just sell the Rembrandt in the faculty lounge.
看吧 问题解决啦
See? Problem solved.
- 他说笑呢 - 问这干嘛 怎么了
- He's being sarcastic. - Why? What's wrong?
没什么 只是在想要是钱花光了咋办
Nothing. Just playing "What if all the money got spent?"
噢 你敢想象吗
Oh, can you imagine? -
那样我们就得取消所有其他校园活动
We'd have to cancel every other school event,
只办摔跤宴
starting with the wrestling banquet,
然后那些个亢奋的精神病患者就会把你们的头给拧下来
and those hopped-up psychos would rip your heads off!
然后你们就血流身亡
And then you'd bleed to death,
因为我们也请不起校医了 对吧
'cause we can't afford a school nurse anymore, right?
噢 有牡蛎哎
Ooh! Oysters.
噢 想得美 小子们
Oh! Nice try, boys!
不是你们的错 只是因为 算了快走吧
You guys are cool. Just, uh, move along.
嘿 小卡 你认识一个叫达米安 沃马克的熊孩子吗
Hey, Cam. Uh, do you know a kid named Damien Warmack?
噢 认识啊
Oh, yeah.
- 那个刻薄的小屁孩 - 就是他
- Mean little kid. - Yeah.
他曾狠狠地羞辱过我
He fat shamed my whole defensive line.
说什么没有什么比眼睁睁看着
There's nothing more sad than watching
一个曾经让人闻风丧胆的中卫把巴豆从沙拉里剔出来更悲哀的了
a once terrifying nose tackle pick croutons out of his salad.
噢 天呐 我好纠结啊
Oh, God, I'm so conflicted.
一个同性恋小屁孩竟敢欺负橄榄球运动员了
A gay kid is now bullying football players,
我想 你知道的 好像也算是种进步了
which I guess, you know, seems like progress,
只不过是不好的那种
but the wrong kind of progress.
- 你想要个 - 噢
- Would you like a... - Oh!
听我解释 蒜末烤面包大部分都掉在地上了哟
In my defense, bruschetta mostly ends up on the floor anyway.
小卡 我想你可能
Cam, I think you might be
对这个所谓的恶作剧反应过激了点
more worried about this prank than you need to be.
我只是想不明白为什么他们会想捉弄我
Well, I just don't understand why they want to prank me.
我原以为他们喜欢我来着
I thought they liked me.
他们当然喜欢你啊
Of course they like you.
怎么能捉弄一个你讨厌的人呢
You can't prank someone you don't like.
那就是 那就是纯粹地恶意攻击了
That's... that's just assault.
但是捉弄你只是他们表达爱你
But pranking you is their bizarre way
的一种偏奇怪的方式罢了
of saying that they love you.
那这算是你忽略我感受的古怪方式吗
Is this your bizarre way of not validating my feelings?
那好吧 我们可以去打保龄球
Okay, we could go bowling.
嗯 昨晚打过啦 现在不是很想打
Hmm. Had my league last night. I'm a little bowled out.
好吧 那打局迷你高尔夫
Fair enough. Round of mini golf?
好主意 等下 我是不是要带上我的青蛙和弹弓
Great idea. Wait up. I'll go get my frog and my slingshot.
然后踩个脚踏车去玩儿啊
We'll hop on our bikes and go down there.
- 那我们可以去吃点什么 - 已经吃过啦
- We could get something to eat. - Already ate.
- 看电影 - 讨厌看台词
- Go to the movies? - Hate the lines.
- 去酒吧怎样 - 那我们要开车大老远跑过去
- How about a bar? - So, we drive across town,
付两倍的价买杯与我手上无异
pay a 200% markup on the same glass of scotch
的苏格兰威士忌吗
I'm holding in my hand right now...
就这样一些个烂醉如泥的娘们就踉跄过来
just so some drunken old broad can stagger over
跟我说我长得像欧尼斯 鲍基尼
and tell me I look like Ernest Borgnine.
你知道吗 还是算了吧
You know what? I'm done trying.
没有一件让你有兴趣和我一起做的事
I'm sorry there isn't a single thing
是我的错
you'd have fun doing with me.
噢 不要这样嘛
Oh, come on!
不要互相伤害嘛
Don't get all hurt.
保证答应你的下个提议
I promise your next idea, I'll say yes to.
- 有必要吗 - 谢啦 杰
- Really? - Thanks, Jay.
你一直想做点什么酷酷的事
You held out for something awesome,
我想我们做到了
and I think we nailed it.
一杯 谢谢
One, please.
8刀 小费的话你看着给就好
That'll be $8, plus whatever tip you feel is appropriate.
一个小时前还免费呢
It was free an hour ago.
你以前还可以把小孩丢
You used to be able to throw a baby
后座 不用儿童安全座椅呢
in the back seat without strapping it in.
朋友 时代变啦
Times change, my friend.
嗨咯 （  ）
Hey, Delgado.
希望这潘趣酒不像你上次在
I hope this punch isn't as watered down
欲望号街车上吊自杀里的表演一样水
as your performance in "A Streetcar Named Desire to Hang Myself."
达米安 你就是 你看着
Damien, you're just... you look...
该死的 我作死地竟好喜欢你这件上衣
Damn it, I hate how much I like that jacket.
嘿
Hey.
- 我知道你在干嘛 - 认识你吗
- I know what you're doing. - Excuse me?
我知道作为一个同志青年有多难
I know how hard it is to be a gay teen.
我高中的时候 只有一个朋友
In high school, I only had one friend.
真的吗
Really?
当王尔德感觉怎么样
What was Oscar Wilde like?
你这是在抨击人
You're lashing out.
因为你很生气 没有安全感
Because you're angry and you're insecure,
你就想让别人也尝尝你受的苦
and you just want everyone else to feel as bad as you do.
也许吧
Maybe.
拜托
But come on.
你应该过得还不错吧 毕竟你长得像迈克尔 法斯宾德
It must've been easier for you looking like Michael Fassbender.
我才不像
I do not look like...
你觉得我像迈克尔 法斯宾德
You think I look like Michael Fassbender?
对啊 如果他再老点 再矮点
Yeah, if he were older and shorter
然后再让凯西 格里芬来演的话
and played by Kathy Griffin.
额
Uh...
嘿 嘿 那个小魔头真是要上天了
Hey, hey. That Damien Warmack kid is so mean.
仗着那些孩子没有安全感
Honing in on these poor kids' insecurities
就伤害他们的自尊心
and then just lacerating them.
我才不像凯西 格里芬呢 你说是吧
I-I don't look like Kathy Griffin, do I?
让我来告诉你什么叫做残忍
I'll tell you what's mean,
我的队员们让我在这等了那个该死的恶作剧一个晚上
is my team making me wait all night for this damn prank.
其实是 米切尔 你想多了
Or, "Mitch, you're being ridiculous.
你本来就很帅
"You're a very handsome man,
如果非要找个女人来扮演你的话
"And if you had to be played by a woman,
那只能是年轻的安·玛格丽特
"It would be a young Ann-Margret."
嘿 教练 -噢 天呐 来吧
- Hey, Coach. - Oh, God! Just do it!
直接来吧
Just do it!
噢 布朗校长 对不起 对不起 我以为
Oh, Principal Brown, sorry. Sorry, I thought...
我以为你就是那个恶作剧
I thought you were the prank.
恶作剧 噢 不是的
Prank? Oh, no.
可能我有点儿误会了
That was a little misunderstanding on my part.
其实是他们要整的是那个新来的教练
Turns out the new wrestling coach is being pranked.
对 他们会把他
Yeah, they're gonna do that thing where
他转个好几圈
you spin a guy around a bunch of times,
然后当他晕圈的时候
you get him good and dizzy,
把他绑在上树上 度过整个周末
and then you tie him to a tree for the weekend.
噢 天呐 你都不阻止他们吗
Oh, God. Shouldn't you stop them?
我也想啊 但他们最近老是在我的车位上停车
I would, but he's been parking in my spot lately.
那这样的话他们就不会整我了
I guess it's a relief they're not pranking me.
对啊 你终于可以放心了
Yes. You can finally relax.
是吗
Can I?
就在这个新来的才来了几个月之后
Knowing Coach Wilson's only been here seven months?
还从来不给队员带自制的香蕉面包
He's never brought his team homemade banana loaf,
他们就在乎他到想要整他了吗
and yet they care enough to terrorize him?
好了 你是不是思想有问题啊
Okay, you're gonna have to land on a position.
我只是不明白如果不是要整我的话
I just don't understand why they begged me to be here
他们请我来干嘛
if they're not gonna prank me.
因为他们敬爱你
Because they love you,
你真的改变了他们的人生
and you're making a real difference in their lives.
噢 真是 我
Oh, well, I-I...
我只是开玩笑的 因为他们觉得你好欺负
I'm just kidding. They think you're a pushover,
而且你在这儿的话 他们就什么坏事儿就能干了
and with you here, they can get away with anything.
这太不像话了 因为我 绝对不漏判任何一件坏事
That's ridiculous, because nothing gets past me.
请来一杯 谢谢
Excuse me. Thank you.
-嗯哼 -你在干嘛
- Mm-hmm. - What is that?
看好了
Look at this.
噢
Oh.
我要把这些都倒进排水沟
I'm gonna go pour this down the drain.
干杯
Cheers.
玩得很开心哈
Having fun?
嘿 我只是在撑门面而已
Hey, I'm just trying to keep up appearances.
如果我慌了了 大家都慌了了
If I panic, everybody panics.
你卖饮料买了多少钱
How much money did you make at the drink station?
只卖了大概200美元
Only about $200.
够了
That's enough.
我一在乡村俱乐部的小跟班
A caddy at the country club where I work
向我推荐了汉兹戴尔的赛狗场
knows this dog track in Hindsdale.
赔率是40:1
There's 40-to-1 odds on a greyhound,
-惠比特犬 超级...
- Whippet Good, who... -
好了 钱全赔了
Okay, the money's gone.
就一次
One time.
- 不 太逗比了 - 就试一次嘛
- No, it's stupid. - Just try it.
- 士可杀不可辱 - 旁边又没人
- I'm not doing it. - No one else is around.
-我不管 -拜托 我来起头
- I don't care. - Come on, I'll start.
呜噫 呜噫 呜噫
A-weem-o-weh, a-weem-o-weh, a-weem-o-weh, a-weem-o-weh
呜噫 在那密密的丛林里
a-weem-o-weh, In the jungle
出去 我们去玩儿别的
Get out. We're doing something else.
有人看上你啦
Somebody thinks you're cute.
拜托克莱尔 这又不是在高中
Claire, please, this isn't high school.
噢 不 等一下 这真的是在高中
Well, no, wait a minute. It is high school.
-哟 -好了
- Mm. - Okay.
好吧 所以说到底是谁
All right, so who is it?
我最爱的是一台1929年的烘焙箱
My favorite is a 1929 Bread Master.
有的人可能会说
Some people might say
收集老式烤箱是个无聊的爱好
that collecting vintage toasters is a crumby hobby.
谢谢
Thank you.
玛乔丽 我刚刚和布朗校长聊天
Marjorie, I was just talking to Principal Brown,
他对你有意思哦 姑娘
and he into you, girl.
真的吗 他可是比20世纪30年代的阳光烤炉还要火辣啊
Really? He's hotter than a 1930s Sunbeam Toastrite.
-憋说话
- Don't.
我现在不方便说话 妈妈
I can't talk right now, Mom.
没有 这个周六我没有一个人在家
No, I'm not home alone on a Saturday night.
我在一个舞会上 有个男孩子喜欢我哦
I'm at a dance, and a boy likes me.
我们真是牵线高手
We good at this!
你为什要用这种腔调说话
Why are you talking like that?
-我也不知道 -
- I don't know. -
你们好 嗨 嘿
Excuse me, hi. Hey.
我真不知道该怎么办才好
I don't know exactly how to do this,
能被您垂青真是我的荣幸
but I'm very flattered by your interest in me,
其实吧 我对你也有相同的感觉
and just so you know, the feeling is mutual.
什么
What?
不知道能否赏脸去露营 我有帐篷
I don't know if you're into camping, but I can get a tent.
我是有夫之妇 另一边屁股还在家里呢
I'm married. My rear end is at home.
我说的是 玛乔丽
I meant Marjorie.
噢
Oh!
噢 不不 她太过热情了
Oh, no. She's way too intense.
不 而且每当你想到
No. And once you've imagined yourself
自己坐在篝火旁 为歌洛迪娅吹着竖笛
sitting by a campfire playing your clarinet for Gloria...
玛乔丽喜欢户外露营
Marjorie loves the outdoors.
对啊 她连露营烤箱都有
Yes, she even has a camping toaster.
她是个很不错的女性 但是 我才45岁
She is a super lady, but, guys, I'm only 45.
我还憧憬者烟火浪漫夜呢
I'm holding out for fireworks.
噢 恶魔来了
Oh, here comes Damien.
千万不要告诉她我以为歌洛迪娅对我有意思
Do not tell him that I thought I had a shot with Gloria.
我妈妈不相信布朗校长喜欢我
My mom doesn't believe that Principal Brown likes me.
你们能和她说吗
Can you tell her?
歌洛迪娅
Gloria?
我在电话里说的英语不太好
My phone English no so good.
-去吃冰淇淋怎么样 -太冷了
- How about ice cream? - Too cold.
- 咖啡 - 太晚了
- Coffee? - Too late.
噢 等一下 我真是蠢
Oh, wait a minute. I'm such an idiot.
我忘了还有克林特·伊斯特伍德的怀旧剧场
I forgot about the Clint Eastwood retrospective
接着可以品尝苏格兰美酒
followed by the scotch tasting
还有70年代的著名运动员和我们讲
where famous athletes from the '70s tell stories
扬斯敦过去的故事
about how life used to be in Youngstown.
- 真的吗 - 假的
- Really? - No!
根本不可能
It doesn't exist.
你想要的根本不可能有
What you want does not exist.
你干嘛啊
What are you doing?
我不管你想怎么样
I don't care what you do,
但是我要去参加舞会
but I'm going into that dance.
我喜欢看孩子们盛装出席 假装自己是个大人
I like to see the kids all dressed up and happy
时快快乐乐的样子
and trying to look older than they are.
我的初吻就是在高中舞会上
The first girl I ever kissed was at a high school dance.
噢
Huh.
那晚我真的唱了“狮王今夜眠”
It was actually to "The Lion Sleeps Tonight."
这可能就是为什么这首歌一直在我脑中挥之不去吧
I guess that's why it was in my head.
狮王那晚彻夜难眠
Let's just say the lion did not sleep that night.
像个疯子一样往肚子里狂灌汽水儿
I was slamming Mountain Dews like a wild man.
玛莎 古尔丁
Marsha Goulding.
年轻时候疯狂迷恋她
I had this huge crush on her.
最后鼓励勇气邀请她参加春节嘉年华
Finally got my nerve up to ask her to the Spring Fling.
第一次跳舞 我很慌张 踩了她好几下
First dance, I was terrified. I'm tromping all over her feet.
但是慢慢的 舞步越来越轻畅
But as the dances went on, it got easier,
就在山姆 库克的 你如此真心 唱到一半的时候
and right in the middle of Sam Cooke singing "You Send Me,"
我亲了她
I went for it.
我很惊讶她也亲了我
I was just so surprised she kissed me back.
好了 你的初吻再也不回来了
Well, you can't have your first kiss again,
但是你的下一个吻在那儿
but you can have your next one right in there.
噢 什么鬼 给歌洛迪娅一个惊喜（吓）
Oh, what the hell. Give Gloria a thrill.
太好了 乔 因为你使她完整
That's great, Jay, 'cause you complete her.
你使她完整了
You complete her.
你是这个笑话的笑点
- You're the butt of this joke.
把毛衣给我
Give me the sweater.
马乔里又聪明又有条理
Marjorie is smart and organized,
如果你需要洗手液或创可贴
and if you ever need hand sanitizer or a Band-Aid,
她都随身带的有
she always has it on her.
她就是一个性感 火辣的便携式药房
She's like a sexy, sexy drugstore.
她可爱极了
She's as cute as a button.
像是成人版的大头娃娃
Like a grown-up Cabbage Patch doll.
- 耶 - 耶 那看起来
- Yeah. - Yeah, that seems like
会很有聊噢
it'd be a whole lot of e-mails.
这就很难办了
It's a hard pass.
但是 布朗校长 你知道他们怎么说
But, Principal Brown, you know what they say
一个热心家务事的母亲吗
about a mom who's enthusiastic in the streets.
从来没有这种说法
That's not a saying.
为什么你们两个
Why are the two of you
突然关心起我的感情生活来了
suddenly so interested in my love life, anyway?
因为我们关心你啊
Because we care.
你都不知道我的大名吧
You don't even know my first name.
不 我们知道
Yes, we do.
是 额 普林斯吧
It's, um... Prince?
你真说的出口
Lucky guess.
我在烧烤台那里
I was over at the carving station,
我想 你知道谁爱吃牛肋排吗
and I thought, "You know who'd love some prime rib?
是普林斯 布朗校长呢
"Principal Prince Brown."
噢
- Oh. -
马乔里 我担心
Marjorie, I'm afraid
你和我是一场失败配对游戏中的炮灰
you and I are pawns in a very sick game
被这两人撮合的
being orchestrated by these two.
他们非常努力的把我们凑成一对
They're working very hard to put us together,
我不知道为什么
and I don't know why.
我从没看过她们对其他事这么上心
I've never seen them work very hard in anything,
除了想从志愿者活动里开小差之外
except getting out of volunteering.
嘿 公正地讲 我们可自愿做很多事呢
Hey, to be fair, we volunteer for plenty of things.
是的 你不记得我拿着水管洗车吗
Yeah, don't you remember me holding a hose at the car wash?
是的 每个人都记得
Yeah, everybody remembers that.
所以你对我不感兴趣咯
So you're not interested in me?
好吧 我们一直是工作伙伴
Well, we've always had a working relationship,
我想我对你没有过那种想法
and I guess I've just never thought of you in that way.
没把我看成一个女人吗
As a woman?
当我工作时 我屏蔽掉那方面的想法
When I'm at work, I turn off that part of myself.
噢
Oh.
啊 现在我兴致勃勃了
Uh, it has turned back on.
- 好吧 - 噢
- Okay. - Oh.
噢 我要去检查那 安全出口
Oh, I'm gonna check the... the fire exits.
我们去抬下椅子
We're going to stack chairs.
随便吧
Whatever.
我有主意了
I've got it.
我们组建一个假的仪乐队
We start a fake marching band
然后得到乐器的经费
and get the money for the instruments up front.
你说的就是和 音乐奇才 这部电影一模一样的剧情吧
You just described the exact plot of "The Music Man."
- 那会发生什么呢 - 赢得四座托尼奖
- How'd that turn out? - Won four Tonys.
电影里是五座 额
Five. Ugh.
你怎么能容许这发生啊
How could you let this happen?
我不知道 当我正在直播我的早餐时
I don't know. You were texting me
你就发短信来了
while I was live streaming my breakfast, and...
等一下
Wait a minute.
我确实说了是800美金吧
I did say $800.
看
Look.
噢 我的天 这全是我的错
Oh, my God, this is all my fault.
好吧 好吧 好吧
Well, well, well.
看起来傻瓜另有其人哦
Looks like the dunce cap is on the other foot.
嘿
Hey!
和你一样体型的动物吃的是什么呢
Is what an animal your size grazes on.
吃的是干草
Hay is...
你胖的像头牛
You're a cow.
好吧
Okay.
你的体重和体型很搭
You're the perfect weight for your frame.
嘿
Hey.
又一个损人的骄傲时刻呢
Another proud moment for the struggle.
额 娘娘腔来了
Ugh. Here she comes.
马丁 卢瑟女王大人 是的
Martin Luther Queen, yes.
无论如何 想放马过来吧
By all means, tell me about the struggle.
好的 你个小婊男
Okay, you nasty little twink.
你欠我太多了
You owe everything to me
包括那些在你出现之前的同志们
and all the gays that came before you.
因为这是我们为此奋斗的所有
It's because of everything we fought for
而你却穿着你的增高鞋垫
that you get to snark your way through high school
在学校里为所欲为
with lifts in your shoes
而不是被推倒在储物柜里面过着担惊受怕的日子
instead of spending it terrified, shoved in a locker.
我说的可真是棒呢
I was really proud of that.
哇
Wow.
我只想让你知道
Just so you know.
在洗澡前用干刷子去去角质
Exfoliating with a dry brush pre-shower
会使你的脸看起来没那么糟心
will really help you with all of this.
会使你看起来又回到50岁了呢
It'll make you look 50 again.
我对他后面说的话感到不是很开心
I'm not really proud of what came next.
你推我的样子都好娘
You shove like a girl!
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我们要支付风笛手的工钱
The piper needs to be paid.
你还请了个风笛手吗
You hired a piper?
不 我弄错了 我需要接受后果
No. I made a mistake, and I need to accept the consequences.
同学们 大家请听我讲讲呢
Classmates, could I have everyone's attention, please?
我有一些令人心烦的消息
I have some troubling news.
我知道你们都认为我是国民老公
I know you may all think of me as the golden boy,
败家子 富二代
the prodigy, the wunderkind.
你是哪位啊
Who are you?
说得好
Indeed.
我也觉得我不认识自己了
I'm not sure I know anymore.
我们出了点小状况
We have a little situation,
我只想站出来说几句话
and I just want to be as up front as I can.
等一下
Hold on a minute.
我是主席
I'm the President.
应该我来说
I should do this.
我们需要为一位急需资金的同学筹集8000美元
We need to raise $8,000 for a classmate in need.
如果我们筹不到这笔钱 他可能就永远不能直立行走了
If we don't get this money, he may never walk again.
我们要弄个众筹项目 如果你想给你的舞伴展示
We're gonna make a Kickstarter, and if you want to show
你是一个感性而富有爱心的人
your date you're the kind of sensitive, caring person
从而被奖励一些亲亲抱抱的话
who deserves to be rewarded in a physical way,
你会慷慨掏钱的
you'll give generously.
哇 你说谎不脸红啊
Wow, you're a good liar.
我收回我的话 你真的配做个主席
I take it back. You deserve to be President.
我们就不应该把那个小混蛋
We never should've helped that little punk
从储物柜里弄出来
get out of that locker.
我不知道他会对你的毛衣出言不逊
I didn't know he was gonna be so brutal about your sweater.
- 好吧 交过来
- All right, hand it over.
- 什么 - 这里禁止明火 臭小子
- What? - This is a blaze-free zone, wastoid.
我监控着全场呢
I got eyes all over this place.
我知道你在那吞云吐雾的干什么
I know what vape is.
- 教练 那只是我的 - 只是你的
- Coach, that's just my... - Just your...
嘿 教练 我能给你说句话吗
Hey, Coach, can I talk to you for a second?
好 什么事
Yeah, what's up?
是的 我 额 只是想让你知道
Yeah, I, uh, just wanted to let you know
那 那是 额 那是他的吸气器
that that's, uh... that's his inhaler.
那是他的 噢
It's his... oh.
你哪根筋不对啊
What is wrong with you?
- 不好意思 - 对不起
- I'm sorry. - Sorry.
因为 我把所有都给了这些孩子
It's just... I give everything to these boys,
而他们还觉得我好欺负
and all they think of me is that I'm a pushover
都不想撇脚的整蛊我一下
not even worthy of a lousy prank.
卡姆 你看到格洛里亚了吗
Cam, have you seen Gloria?
什么 是的 噢 上次我看到她
What? Yeah, oh, last time I saw her,
她就在这呢
she was somewhere over here.
噢 那是为我准备的
Oh, that was for me!
那本来是想整我的 我的学生是爱我的
That was supposed to be for me! My boys love me!
我只是想读我的书
I just wanted to read my book.
噢 你好啊 我是卢克 邓菲
Oh, hi there. I'm Luke Dunphy,
学生会主席
Student Body President.
- 我是曼尼 - 但是这不是我们的故事
- And I'm Manny... - But this isn't about us.
我们有一个同学 情况危急
We have a classmate who's in a pretty bad spot.
但是事情可能会有转机的
But it doesn't have to end that way.
只要你帮助进来 我们就能避免他被打个半死
With your help, we can save him from getting beaten up.
从 从疾病的打击中
By... by his disease.
一场不该由一个孩子去斗争的疾病
A disease no kid should have to wrestle with.
我们只需要筹集8000美元
We just need to raise $8,000 to...
或者9000美元来帮助他买一台超级无敌贵的治疗机械
Or $9,000 to get him that super deluxe treatment.
我们只需要8000美元
We only need $8,000...
我是卢克 邓菲 我支持这场募捐
I'm Luke Dunphy, and I approve this message.